okay well R Gupta is with us now senior
portfolio manager India Equity
specialist at manual Life Investment
Management uh ra you know it's been a
fantastic June near 7% gains for the
Nifty and now we are in the second half
into July earnings budget so a lot to
sort of uh track going
forward uh you know just a quick word on
uh let's just look at the earnings right
it services will be first off the block
and there is widespread expectation that
it'll be better maybe because it's a
it's a weaker base or whatever but and
especially compared to q1 Q uh q1 is
usually better seasonally as well uh
what's a s sense it Services index in
June was up almost about 8% or so
R yeah hi good morning yes earning is
going to start L by it and I do think
the it companies coton cter buses can
deliver somewhat better growth but for
the full year the view is that uh the
growth in the top line still is going to
be a bit subdued probably you know High
single is what uh we we can see there
having said that I think the it as a
sector they underperform the market and
it sector generates a lot of cash and
they have a pretty good and well-known
dividend policy so the the the it stocks
I think at the at the end of the day
will continue to behave as defensive as
far as Indian market is concerned at
least in the shorter term over the
medium to long term I think the negative
impacts of in software services at least
in two to three time of the of the
artifici intelligence
will become clear I think in that case
one would see the Top Line will continue
to grow at a slower level for some time
margins what happens we will see but in
the shorter time frame let's say
525 I think these stocks continue to
beave quite
defensively okay Rana hi good morning
and thanks for joining in its record
highs for our Market I wonder your
thoughts on Reliance Industries
particularly because there was Telecom
was the big talking point last week
right with those tariff hikes finally
coming through and there's a sort of a
breakout happening in some of these
Telecom names like Reliance is there
still more to go on the upside in the
medium
term unfortunately I won't be able to
comment on the stock specific but on the
Telecom I think this uh hike was broadly
expected but if you look at the stock
move I think Reliance hike tariffs
better than expected whereas the other
company vti hike tarff lower than
expected and you saw the you the stock
reactions but I think overall the point
is for the sector right now the Tariff
hikes are coming through and there may
be short-term reaction the stock price
is depending on the expectation but the
broader picture is this is one industry
which is deflating where the top lines
are moving up and this is a largely
fixed cost industry and all the leading
players baring the you know maybe ID I
think BH and Reliance all the leading
players they have got their C in so I
think going forward for the sector we
will see is that uh Top Line going up
cost not as much so therefore that
should lead to pretty good cash flows
for the sector and the leading
confidence in the sector all right hi R
good morning good to see you in what
about the Outlook from year on for the
second half of the year do you expect
India to be a relative outperformer in
comparison to Global markets given that
we have the elections that are out of
the way there are expectations with
regard to the budget and earnings could
look reasonably strong your
take yes India could still do do well as
compared to the global markets in fact
if you look at include the develop
Market that makes India is just about
you know average because or slightly
better or slightly less because us has
been doing so doing so well but I think
as if you compare India energy markets
it's clearly a bit of a former because
if you look at the political
geopolitical scenario across all the
energy markets there are worries on
inflation worries on fiscal deficit in
certain countries uh worries on slowing
growth I think in that entire Val India
with its political stability and with
its economic you know policy and all
that stand out quite a bit having said
that I think few points need to be made
I think in India the you know the
Industrials the real estate the
PSU these cyclical stocks have done very
well and rightly so because government
shity was you know on the on on the cafe
side uh on the other hand I think the
the private Banks the consumer durable
stocks they have underperformed by a
wide margin so I think uh going forward
as the budget happens this time
government has got a lot of fiscal room
we would expect some allocation to uh
Revenue expenditure while maintaining C
expenditure but I think incremental
Delta for Rue expenditure should be
better and that should be positive for
some of the consumer to and private
banking names which has underperformed
so far okay R we will let you go on that
note thank you so much for joining us
and giving us a quick take on what you
expect you know could be the move in the
Indian markets let's St into a quick
break on the other side we kick start a
brand new week with our entire research
team joining in to help us with the list
of top 10 stocks stay with us